我们不是见过吗
Haven't we met somewhere before?
不是吧  就这么泡我啊
Really? That's your line?
不是泡你
It's not a line.
我今早在咖啡厅见过你
I saw you this morning at the coffee bean,
下午又在健身房看见你  现在又碰到了
and then this afternoon at the gym, and now here.
你为什么跟踪我
Why are you following me?
好做这个
So I could do this.
没事
It's okay.
你的主动脉已被切断  一切很快就会结束
Your aorta's been severed, so this will all be over very soon.
别抗拒
Don't fight it.
看着我漂亮的褐色眼睛  让意识模糊吧
Just look into these pretty brown eyes and drift away.
亲爱的  你又把头发点着了吗
Babe, did you set your hair on fire again?
就那一次诶  没有啦
That was one time. And no. No, no.
我就是帅到冒烟而已
I'm just, uh, so good-looking, I'm literally smoking hot.
好了  你拿着什么呢
Okay, what do you have?
-就是...  -让我看看
- That...is just, uh... - Let me see.
-我看看  -等等
- Just a little... - Wait a second.
好吧
All right. Okay.
天呐
Oh, my god.
第一天  感觉如何
First day. How are you feeling?
兴奋  担心  以及之间的一切
Um...exhilarated and frightened and everything in between.
真希望你能一起来
I wish that you were coming with me.
亲爱的  我们讨论过了  我能干什么啊
Oh, sweetie, we talked about this. What am I gonna do?
坐在你办公室外给你拿咖啡吗
Sit outside your office and fetch you coffee?
嗯  你拿东西很棒的  我调教得好
Yeah, you're great at fetching. I've trained you well.
这对我们来说是好的改变
This is a good change for us.
是吗
Is it?
绝对的
Yes. Absolutely.
再说  我花了那么多钱
And besides, with all the money I spent
装修我的私家侦探办公室
on the remodeling of my P.I. Office,
我总得接点案子才能平衡账目
I got to take some cases so I can write that place off.
好了  开动吧[挖]
Now, come on. Dig in.
不  我紧张得吃不下
No, I'm so nervous I couldn't eat.
谁叫你吃了  我说的是"挖"
Who said anything about eating? I said, "Dig in."
好吧
Okay.
你是叫我挖吗
Like "Dig" dig in, right?
-嗯嗯  -好吧
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Okay. All right. Um...
来吧
Full on.
继续
Keep going.
就这样
Like that.
什么嘛
What?
本该是枚解码戒指的
That was supposed to be a decoder ring.
天呐  好漂亮啊
Oh, my god. This is so beautiful.
你能接一下吗
Um, would you mind getting that?
嗯  给
Yeah, yeah. Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
天呐
Oh, my god.
贝克特警监电话
Captain Beckett's phone.
请找凯瑟琳·贝克特
Uh...Katherine Beckett, please.
好的  请稍等
Of course. Please wait just one moment.
-跟你换  谢谢  -给
- Trade you. Thank you. - Here you go.
我是贝克特
Yeah, this is Beckett.
好的  明白
Okay. Understood.
嗯  我不感兴趣
Yeah. You know what? I'm not interested,
你直接把我划掉吧
so why don't you take me off the list?
谢谢
Thanks.
电话推销
Telemarketers.
真该颁布更严格的法律管制他们
I swear there should be tougher laws against them.
要不是你拒绝了
Well, if you hadn't turned down the chance
竞选参议员的机会  你本可以做到的
to run for state senate, you could have passed some.
我好喜欢  我会珍惜的
I love this. I'm gonna cherish this.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  我要去总局开会
Okay, I have got a meeting at 1pp.
-震住他们  -谢谢
- Knock 'em dead. - Thanks.
兄弟  你干吗呢
Bro, what are you doing?
你知道我抢到了贝克特的桌子
You know I got dibs on Beckett's desk.
我们猜拳吧
I will play you knife, gun, kevlar for it.
好啊
Let's do this.
-刀  -枪
- Knife. - Gun.
你个傻子  带刀参加枪战吗
You fool, you brought a knife to a gun fight?
嘭
Blam.
-三局两胜  -没门  闪人
- Two out of three. - No way. Kick rocks.
哈维  我们真可悲
Javi, we're pathetic.
不  你才可悲  你分到了差劲的桌子
No, you're pathetic. You're the one who got the crappy desk.
不  我是说  我们还抢桌子呢
No, look, I mean, here we are moving desks.
而别人都往上爬了
Everyone else is moving up.
盖茨  升副局长
Gates, she's the new deputy chief,
贝克特  升警监
Beckett, she's the new captain.
-怎么  -什么时候轮到我们
- So? - So when's it gonna be our turn?
升职  涨工资
Get promoted, make more money?
兄弟  怎么突然说起这个
Bro, where's this coming from?
珍妮又怀了  我们昨晚得知的
Jenny's pregnant again. We found out last night.
太棒了  恭喜啊
That's great! Congratulations!
是好事吧
That is great, right?
当然  太棒了
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's wonderful.
但我又要多糊一张口了
But it's also another mouth to feed,
还得买衣服
another body to clothe,
更别提大学学费了
and don't get me started on college tuition.
凯文  你能不能就消停一会儿
Kevin, ca-can't you just for one second...
先庆祝一下  再为钱的事紧张
...celebrate before you start stressing about money again?
-有时候喘口气也挺好  -太棒了
- Sometimes it's good to just breathe... - Yes!
来凶案了
Got ourselves a homicide.
祈祷会有加班费
Fingers crossed for overtime pay.
兄弟  你不对劲啊
Bro, there's something wrong with you.
您有事吗
Can I help you?
当然有  伙计
You sure as hell can, buddy.
我是弗兰可·曼奇尼
I'm Franco Mancini!
总算见到你了  快来
Nice to finally meet you. Bring it on in.
来拥抱下
Come here.
真是好消息啊  对吧理查
Great news, huh, Ricky?
我老婆睡的是我弟弟
My wife's sleeping with my brother,
不是我的厨子  真是松了口气
Not my personal chef -- what a relief.
不好意思  你太太跟你弟弟有染
Uh, I'm sorry. Y-y-your wife is having an affair with your brother
而你还挺高兴的
and you're happy about it?
拜托  弟弟我还有四个
Hell, I got four other brothers,
但我的厨子可是万中无一的
But my chef is one in a million.
能吃上他做的辣蛤蜊简直死了都值
His spicy clams are to die for.
再次感谢你破了我的案子  理查
Thanks again for solving my case, Ricky.
你和你的助理
You and your associate.
助理
Associate?
请你在前台等等好吗  我马上就来
Could you wait out in reception? I'll be with you in a sec.
阿丽克西斯  我不想说
Uh, Alexis, I don't want to say
你得解释解释
you have some explaining to do,
可你真得解释解释
but I think you have some explaining to do.
等等  我是不是忘了告诉你
Wait, did I forget to tell you
我在帮你处理私家侦探的案子
I've been working P.I. Cases for you?
你肯定是忘了
Must have slipped your mind.
对了  他们把这里改建得真好啊  是吧
Hey, didn't the guys do a fantastic job remodeling the place?
我知道  是吧
I know, right?!
但你在转移话题
But you're changing the subject.
我知道  但你看
I know. But check it out.
只要拨一下这本《爱伦·坡小说集》...
Pull on "The complete works of Edgar Allan Poe," and...
我的天
Oh, my god!
这比我想象得酷多了
This turned out so much cooler than I thought it would!
等等  他们有没有在桌上安装....
Wait, did they do the thing on the desk with the...?
显然弹簧是有轨迹的
Obviously the spring has a trajectory --
我会...好了  说回到你
I'll make the -- okay, back to you.
你为啥  为啥要调查我的案子
Why -- why are you working my cases?
事实上  都是你的错
Truth is, it's all your fault.
你背着我在我办公室当起了老板
You set up shop in my office behind my back,
-结果还是我的错  -没错
- and it's my fault? - Exactly.
一个月前  你让我来帮你的工头开门
A month ago, when you sent me here to open the place for your foreman,
正好来了个潜在的客户
a potential client came by.
我起了好奇心  所以我就说我是你助手
I was intrigued, so I sort of said I was your associate,
然后我就不小心破了那案子
And then I kind of solved the case.
从那之后  我已经又结了三个案子了
Since then, I've closed three others.
阿里克西斯  你不能...你结了四个案子
Alexis, you can't just -- you closed four cases?
居然比我结的还多
That's more than I have.
我知道  你得提高水平了
I know. Step your game up.
那你的大学课程怎么办
W-what about your college courses?
拜托  我应付得来
Oh, please. I've got that handled.
而且  我伪造了你的签名
Plus, I forged your signature
可以凭做实习生拿到学分
to make sure I got school credit for being an intern.
是埃斯波西托  我得接
Okay, that's Esposito. I have to take this.
不过你的事可还没说完
But we are not done talking.
很好  我们得讨论下
Good, we need to discuss
我在公司的红利分成
my profit participation in the company.
-卡塞尔  -埃斯波西托
- Castle? - UH, E-Esposito.
还好吗  伙计  新女上司对你怎么样
How you doing, buddy? How's the new boss lady treating you?
她在无视我
She's ignoring me.
就跟他生命中的其他女人一样
Just like every other woman in his life.
闭嘴
Shut up.
总之  你老婆没接电话
So, your wife is not answering her cell,
我们需要她多派点警员过来
and we need her authorization for more officers down here.
-她跟你在一起吗  -抱歉
- Is she with you? - Oh, I'm sorry.
她去总局开会了  出什么事了
She's at a meeting at 1pp. What's going on?
我们在办一个案子  有兴趣吗
We're working on a case. You interested?
我也想  可我这蒸蒸日上的
I'd love to, but I'm a little busy
私家侦探业务有点忙
with my thriving P.I. Business.
并没有  我把案子都结了
Not really. I closed all the cases.
不过既然你们需要人  我就忙里抽闲...
But since you're desperate, I'll rearrange my hectic schedule...
帮你们参谋参谋吧
...and, uh, lend you my expertise.
拜托
Come on.
这就像昆汀·塔伦蒂诺的电影成真了
Looks like a tarantino film came to life in here.
是啊  见见主演吧  这是格雷格·米诺索
Yeah. Now meet our stars. This is Greg Minoso.
这边是杰克·菲兹
Over here, we got Jake Fitz.
最后  这是达斯汀·钱伯斯
And finally, we come to Dustin Chambers.
还有  他们都带着一样的40口径枪
And check this out. They were each packing identical .40 cals.
我猜他们不是装修队的
I take it they weren't part of the construction crew.
对  按计划  装修要下周才开始
No. Renovation's not scheduled to begin till next week.
好吧  那到底发生了什么
Okay. So, what happened?
其实  我们也还不知道
Truth is, we're not sure yet.
我们只知道上午9:07分有人听到了枪声
What we do know is that gunfire was heard around 9:07 a.m.
持续了一两分钟左右
And continued for a minute or two.
所以他们是自相残杀的
So they shot each other?
不  他们的伤口角度是向下的
Nope, their wounds are from a downward angle,
大概45度左右
Maybe 45 degrees,
也就是说枪击可能均来自那上边
which means they probably all were shot from up there.
没错了  枪手绝对是在这上边的
Yep. The shooter was definitely up here.
9毫米口径的
9 millimeter.
好吧
All right.
他在这里对他们开了枪
Must have capped them from up here,
砰  砰  砰  然后从那个出口逃走了
Boom, boom, boom, and then boogied out that exit.
伙计们
Ew. Guys.
看来枪手也被死者打中了
Looks like our shooter took a bullet from one of the dead guys down there,
靠着墙倒下了  抓着罩单
Falls back up against the wall, grabbing the drop cloth,
给顺手扯下来了
pulling it down with him.
跟医院联系一下  看有没有人
Let's contact hospitals, see if anybody came in...
这是贝克特的
This is Beckett's.
等等  你刚才说什么
Wait. What did you just say?
我今天早晨给她的
I gave it to her this morning.
她来过这
She was here.
告诉我
Tell me.
蕾妮说那是贝克特的血
Lanie said that blood was a match to Beckett's.
那里有好多血啊
But there was so much blood.
好吧
O-okay.
好吧  不过这可是贝克特
Okay, but this is... this is Beckett we're talking about.
是的  是的  她很坚强
Yeah, yeah. She's as tough as they come.
没错  所以说她一定是打死了那三个人
Exactly. So, she must have shot those three guys.
可既然她没有联系咱们
And since she hasn't contacted us,
可以假定是他们的同伴绑架了她
we can assume that their partners abducted her.
可是为什么呢
But why?
我们要查一下这些死掉枪手的背景
We need to dig into the backgrounds of those dead shooters.
找出他们的同伙是谁
We need to find out who they're working with.
问题就在这  查不到  他们的证件是假的
That's the thing. We can't. Their I.D.s are all fake.
而且系统里也查不到他们的指纹
And their prints aren't in the system.
卡塞尔  你知道贝克特去剧院干什么吗
Castle, do you have any idea what Beckett was doing at that theater?
她本该去总局的
She was supposed to be at 1PP.
我跟盖茨谈过了
I talked to Gates.
根本没有贝克特的预约
Beckett didn't have anything on the books.
这么说她骗了我
So she lied to me?
伙计们  我查到了其中一个死者的信用卡
Guys, I got a hit on one of the dead shooter's credit cards.
他在一个网站上租了一个短期公寓
He rented a short-term apartment through an online site.
纽约警局
NYPD!
莱恩  有个死角
Ryan, I got dead space.
卡塞尔  待在那别动
Castle, stay put.
纽约警局
NYPD!
等等
Wait!
她在哪
Where is she?!
贝克特在哪
Where's Beckett?
-纽约警局  别动  -马上趴下
- NYPD! Don't move! - Get on the floor right now!
-趴下  -快趴下
- On the ground! - On the floor right now!
你们看到地上什么样了吗
Have you seen the floor?
你们如果不介意  我还是站着吧
If it's all the same to you, boys, let's do the standing.
坐吧  希普顿小姐
Have a seat, Miss Shipton.
别这么称呼我  叫我海莉
Oh, no, please, call my Hayley.
我让所有摸过我的人都叫我的教名
I insist that anyone who's frisked me use my given name.
好吧  海莉  我搭档和我非常喜欢
Okay, Hayley, my partner and I really enjoyed
看你的档案
reading your file.
亲爱的  我可不止上面写的那样
Oh, sweetie, I'm so much more than words on paper.
从小在伦敦东区长大
Born and raised in east London,
哈克尼区
over in the borough of Hackney.
那里治安不怎么好
Rough area.
那里不是有条街叫"一英里谋杀街"吗
Don't they have a street nicknamed "The murder mile"?
是啊  但也有些风情的
Well, yes. But it's not without its charms.
和你一样  顺说  我喜欢你的口音
Just like you. Love your accent, by the way.
很时髦
Very posh.
你在哪学会的
Where did you learn to speak like that?
肯定不是在她小时候生活的贫民窟里
Not from the slums she grew up in.
而且也绝对不是从你妈妈那学的
And definitely not from your mom,
她被判了20年  快刑满了
who's at the tail end of a 20-year prison bid.
不想步妈妈的后尘
Oh, then not wanting to follow in mum's footsteps,
于是加入了伦敦警察厅
you joined the Metropolitan Police Service.
-结果干得很失败  -是的  他们把你解雇了
- And that was an epic fail. - Yeah, they booted you out
因为你喜欢钻法律的空子
because of your tendency to cut legal corners.
并没有证据
Allegedly.
你为了让一个毒贩子招供
You hung a dealer out of a window
就把他挂在窗外
in order to get a confession?
我是把他挂在窗外
Did I hang him out the window?
还是我把他从窗外救上来了呢
Or did I save him from falling out said window?
这很难说  也很难证明
It's hard to tell. It's even harder to prove.
我们很幸运  不用去证明
Well, lucky for us, we don't have to prove
你躲在那个公寓里
that you were hiding in that apartment.
躲  不是  是迷路了
Hiding? No. Lost.
其实我当时是在找星巴克
I was looking for a Starbucks, actually.
通常是很容易找到的
Usually they're so easy to find.
你怎么认识租了那间公寓的人
How do you know the guy who rented that apartment?
不像以前坐在这张椅子上的那些傻蛋们
Unlike the imbeciles who usually sit in this chair,
我知道自己的权利  所以我要走了
I know my rights, so I would like to leave now.
不行  我不同意
No. I don't think so.
纽约警局的一名警监失踪了  还死了三个人
We got a missing NYPD captain, as well as three dead bodies,
所以你赶紧交代吧
So you should start talking right now.
我不知道什么...
I don't know anything...
拜托  海莉  别装了
Hey, come on, Hayley. You can do better than that.
我是个自由职业的安保专家
Look, I am just a freelance security specialist.
有家保险公司雇我去抓一名黑客
I was hired by an insurance company to catch a hacker
此人一直在从他们公司的系统中盗取社保号码
who's been stealing social-security numbers from their system.
你为什么出现在那间公寓里
Why were you in that apartment?
我在追查那些
I have been following fake I.D.s
用被盗社保账号制成的假证件
made from the stolen social-security numbers.
昨晚  我收到通知
And last night, I got an alert
有五个假证件在纽约同时被使用了
that five of them had been used together in New York city.
这引起了我的注意  所以我飞过来调查
Caught my attention, so I flew in to investigate.
五个证件  你确定是五个吗
Five I.D.s. You sure it was five?
四男一女
Four men and a woman.
格雷格·米诺索  杰克·菲兹
Greg Minoso, Jake Fitz,
泰·戴德  达斯汀·钱伯斯
Ty Dade, Dustin Chambers,
和苏珊·艾莫里
and Susan Emory.
今天早上九点你在哪里
Where were you at 9:00 A.M. this morning?
到肯尼迪机场的最后一班转机航班上
On final approach to JFK,
我的航班9:30才到
and my flight didn't land until 9:30.
我就知道这么多
And that is all I know.
赶紧去查我的不在场证明
Now go and check my alibi
好让我早点离开这个鬼地方
so that I can get the hell out of here.
谢谢
Thanks.
她有隐瞒
She's hiding something.
我知道
I know.
我们不能就这么放了她
We can't just let her leave.
她有不在场证明  只能放人
Her alibi is solid. We have to.
莱恩
Ryan.
来了
Yeah.
我放倒过你一次  再来一次我也无所谓
I put you down once. I won't hesitate to do it again.
我叫理查德·卡塞尔  失踪的警监是我妻子
My name is Richard Castle. That missing captain is my wife.
这我不知道  我很遗憾
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
遗憾就免了  我需要的是你的帮助
Keep your sorry. Just give me your help.
你并没有把知道的一切都告诉我们
There's more to this story than you're telling us.
现在她受伤而且被绑架了
Now she's been injured and abducted.
这我并不知情
I don't know anything about that.
出价吧  不管多少  我都接受
Name your price. Anything you say, I'll pay it.
我只想找回我妻子
I just want my wife back.
希望你能找到她
I hope you find her.
警员在23大街上一家干洗店旁边
Yo, UNIs found a stolen van with blood in it
发现一辆有血迹的被盗面包车
by a dry-cleaner's on 23rd street.
-找到贝克特了吗  -没
- Any sign of Beckett? - No.
警员发现店主被锁在了里屋
Officers found the owner locked in the back.
他们说一个符合贝克特特征的女性去过
They said a woman matching Beckett's description was there.
你好  我是莱恩警探
Hi. I'm detective Ryan.
这是埃斯波西托警探  还有卡塞尔先生
This is detective Esposito. This is mr. Castle.
给我们讲讲是怎么回事好吗
Can you tell us what happened here?
一男一女闯了进来  女人说她是警察
A lady and man burst in. She said she was cop.
身上到处是血  看起来不太好
Bleeding everywhere. Big mess.
那就是她的衣服
Those are her clothes.
她让那个男人把我锁进卫生间
She told man to lock me in bathroom,
他就照做了  就这样
he did, and that was it.
等等  是她命令的他
Wait, she told him?
你是说那位女性来这里是出于自愿
You're saying that she was here of her own volition?
不是被挟持的吗
Not as a hostage?
被挟持的是我  下命令的才是她
I was hostage. She was in charge.
没错  就是她
Yeah, it's her.
好吧  和她在一起的那个男人
Okay, this man that she was with,
能描述一下他的特征吗
can you describe him?
二十多岁  东印人  大胡子
Uh... late 20s, East Indian, had beard.
知道他的名字吗
Did you catch his name?
不知道  但他情况也不太好
No. But he was in kind of bad shape, too.
头晕头痛  说他需要吃东西
Headaches, dizzy, said he needed to eat.
她跟他说早上他就不该给她打电话
She told him he probably should have gotten breakfast
该去吃早饭
instead of calling her.
贝克特今早确实接到了一个男人的电话
Beckett got a call from some guy this morning.
你知道对方是谁吗
Do you know who she was talking to?
她说是个电话推销员
She said it was a telemarketer.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
这到底是怎么回事啊
What the hell is going on?
好吧  好好想想
All right, let's think.
贝克特接到了一个神秘人的电话
Beckett gets a call from a mystery man.
能追踪这个电话吗
Can we trace the phone?
已经查了  一次性电话打来的
Already checked. Call came from a burner phone.
该死  好吧
Oh, damn it. All right.
她肯定是在剧院见了这个人
She must have met this guy at the theater.
显然他们中了埋伏  贝克特中了枪
Clearly they were ambushed. Beckett gets shot.
但她干掉了对方的三个人
But she manages to take three of them out,
然后和这个人逃走了
and then she and the man escape.
但她没有向警局求援
But she didn't call for backup.
对啊  她为什么不联系我们
Yeah. Why wouldn't she reach out to us?
两位  她可是用针线
Guys, the woman just sewed herself up
缝了伤口
with a needle and thread.
明显是有重大隐情
Clearly something's going on,
而且她不敢联系任何人
and she's afraid to contact anyone.
但是什么隐情呢  什么事能
But what? I me-- I mean, what could it be
让她做出这种事来呢
that would cause her to react like this?
不管是什么  肯定都和这个人有关
Whatever it is, it has to do with this man.
找到神秘人  就能找到贝克特
We find the man, we find Beckett.
好吧  我去找鉴证组在这里搜取指纹
All right, I'll have CSU dust this place for prints.
-也许能确认神秘人的身份  -好
- Maybe we get an I.D. on this guy. - Right.
我送干洗店老板去见画像师
I'll get the dry-cleaner to sit with a sketch artist.
阿丽克西斯  听我说
Hey, Alexis, listen, somet--
爸爸  赶紧回办公室来
Dad, come back to the office now.
怎么了
What's going on?
赶快回来吧  别带别人
Just hurry. And come alone.
好
Right.
警局见了
Uh, I'll -- I'll meet you back at the station.
好
All right.
阿丽克西斯
Alexis?
爸爸  我们在里面
Dad, we're in here.
我们
"We"?
-就是这样  没错  -真的吗
- That's it. That is it. - Yeah?
-真的  -这是怎么回事
- Yes. Okay. - What the hell's going on here?
希望你不介意
Oh, I hope you don't mind.
我只是教她些私家侦探的技巧
I'm just giving her some P.I. lessons.
海莉在教我操纵男人的技巧
Hayley was teaching me the art of manipulating men.
重点是自信和眼神接触
It's all about confidence and eye contact.
如果你用眼神就能诱惑一个男人
Yeah, if you can entice a man with your gaze,
你就能撒谎  偷东西  出轨 诸如此类
You can lie, steal, cheat, what have you.
我妻子还在努力求生
My wife is out there fighting for her life.
你为什么要浪费我的时间
Why are you wasting my time?
什么  你怎么不告诉我
Wait, what? Why didn't you tell me?
抱歉  我觉得不应该由我来告诉你
Sorry. I figured it wasn't my place.
里克  你之前求我帮忙  现在还需要吗
Now, look, Rick. You asked for my help. You want it or not?
有什么条件
What's the catch?
因为我觉得和你做事  总会有条件的
Cause I'm thinking, with you, there's always a catch.
只有一条  不带警察
There's only one -- no cops.
-为什么不  -目的不同
- Why not? - Differing agendas.
警察服务和保卫这座城市
The cops serve and protect the city.
我服务和保卫自己
I serve and protect me.
好  不带警察
Fine. No cops.
爸爸  贝克特怎么了
Dad. What happened to Beckett?
她受伤了  并且正在逃亡
She's hurt, and she's on the run.
为了躲谁
From whom?
我不知道  这跟和她在一起的男人有关系
I don't know. It has something to do with a man she's with.
什么男人
What man?
我在这不是吗  你得付出才有回报
Look, I'm here, aren't I? You've got to give to get.
这个神秘男子是谁
Who's this mystery man?
他是东印人  将近30岁  他可能生病了
He's east Indian, in his late 20s. He might be sick.
他头晕  头疼  说他需要吃点东西
He was dizzy, had a headache, said he needed something to eat.
我不知道  你知道什么  海莉
I don't know. What about you, Hayley?
我知道你有事没有告诉我们
I know you're holding back on something.
我有关于剩下两个枪手的线索
I have a lead on the last two shooters.
怎么找到的
How?
我不是仅仅在追踪随机的假身份
Well, I haven't just been chasing random identities.
一个黑客偷了十万个社保账号
A hacker stole 100,000 social-security numbers,
再把它们分为一个个小组
then bundled them into smaller groupings.
他把这些社保账号卖给谁
And who's he selling the bundles to?
黑手党  毒枭  恐怖分子  任君挑选
Mafia, drug cartels, terrorists. Take your pick.
然而  从这一组五名枪手中
However, from the bundle of those five shooters,
我发现他们刚使用了一个新的身份
I've just uncovered that a new identity's been used.
你能追踪它吗
Can you track it?
我已经追踪了
I already have.
几天以前有人用它租了一个储藏柜
It was used to lease a storage locker a few days ago.
这怎么能帮我找到贝克特
And how does this help me find Beckett?
不能  但现在仍然有两个杀手在找她
It doesn't, but there are still two killers hunting her.
如果我们能找到他们
If we can track them down,
我离找到我的黑客更进一步
I get one step closer to my hacker,
你也能救出你妻子
and you get your wife out of harm's way.
这样  我们各取所需
This way, we both get what we want.
好  我们走
All right. Let's go.
爸爸  你在干洗店有没有注意到
Dad, did you notice any candy wrappers or fruit juice,
糖纸  果汁  任何含糖的东西吗
anything with sugar, at the dry-cleaner's?
有一个空苏打罐子  怎么了
Uh, an empty soda can. Why?
我觉得和贝克特在一起的神秘男子
I think Beckett's mystery man might have been having
可能糖尿病发病了
a diabetic incident.
但是根据他的症状  糖分仍然不够
But based on his symptoms, sugar is not enough.
-他需要胰岛素来  -亲爱的  我得走了
- He'll need insulin to regulate -- - honey, I need to go.
我们一会再说这个  好吗
Let's talk about this later, though, okay?
红发妞  别等着你老爸
Red, don't wait for the old man.
如果你找到了什么  继续查下去
If you've got something, follow up on it.
贝克特在逃亡
Look, Beckett's on the run.
她不能去找医生  不能去医院
She can't go to a doctor, can't go to a hospital,
那她怎么去弄胰岛素呢
So how does she get her hands on insulin?
她得想别的办法
She would have to get creative.
这就对了
There you go.
为什么要在后门停车
Why did we park back here?
海莉  我们可以直接从前门进去
Hayley, we can just walk straight through the front door.
那用不着断线钳
There's no bolt cutters required.
你扮演警察的时间太长了  里克
Oh, you've been playing at being a cop too long, Rick.
作为一个私家侦探  你没有警徽  没有搜查令
As a P.I., you don't have a badge, don't have search warrants.
你必须得想别的办法  撒谎  骗人
You've got to get creative, lie, cheat.
偶尔非法入侵一下  对吧
And the occasional b&e, apparently?
是啊  如果必须的话
Yeah, if that's what it takes.
那么  你要怎么做
So, what's it gonna be?
这就对了
Yeah.
我叫阿  斯特赖克  克拉拉·斯特赖克
Hi. My name's Ale-- Stryker. Clara Stryker.
我是紧急事故处理中心的审计员
I'm an auditor with emergency services.
我能为你做什么  斯特赖克小姐
Um...what can I do for you, Ms. Stryker?
我正在调查一通911假警报
I'm looking into a bogus 911 call
从第2大街和第23大街的交界处的干洗店打来的
made near a dry-ceaner's on 2nd and 23rd street.
对  我们报告为恶作剧
Yeah. Uh, right. We reported that as a prank.
我确定你事后进行了完整的盘点
Then I'm sure you performed a complete inventory afterward.
我就当做你不知道你要这么做
I take it you didn't know you needed to?
别担心  我们可以现在做
Don't worry. We can do it now.
斯特赖克小姐  我只是一个试用的急救员
Look, Ms. Stryker, I'm just a probationary E.M.T.
我的主管很快就要回来了
My supervisor's gonna be back any minute now.
这事能不能等一下
Can't this wait?
看上去所有东西都在
Well, looks like everything's in its place.
你把胰岛素放在哪
Where do you keep the insulin?
该死
Shoot.
我们丢了2瓶
We're missing two vials.
那个摄像头有显示屏吗
Do you have a monitor for the camera?
有
Yeah.
回放到那通电话的时候
Play back the time of the call.
怎么回事
What the hell?
暂停一下
Freeze it.
斯特赖克小姐  我会有麻烦吗
Ms. Stryker, am I gonna get in trouble for this?
这是我们之间的小秘密
We'll keep it our little secret.
这些人到底是谁
Who the hell are these people?
总之找找可以用来追踪这些人的东西
Just look for anything that we can use to track these guys.
这些和剧院里那些枪手用的
These are the same .40-calibers
40口径枪一模一样
the shooters in the theater had.
你在给谁发信息  警察吗
Who did you just text? The cops?
我们有言在先  你食言了
We had a deal. You shook on it.
如果你想要我遵守诺言
If you wanted a binding agreement,
我们应该打勾勾
we should have pinky-sweared.
你多大了  四岁吗
What are you, 4?
海莉  发生了什么
Hayley, what happened?
我被揍惨了
Ooh. I got my ass kicked.
什么事
Hey. What's up?
爸爸  我追踪到了一辆贝克特
Dad, I was able to track Beckett
和那个神秘男子上过的出租车
and that mystery man to a taxi.
你真是太棒了  那好
You are the best. Okay. Um...
现在我们只需要给出租车公司打电话
Now all we have to do is call the cab company,
问问他们去了哪里
figure out where they went.
已经问了  他们去了州北的一座监狱
Already did. They went to a prison upstate.
真的  她还在那吗
Really? Is she still there?
不  但她探视了一名犯人  威廉·布莱肯
No, but she visited an inmat -- William Bracken.
布莱肯
Bracken?
你妻子为什么去探视一个犯罪的前参议员
Okay, why is your wife visiting a disgraced former senator?
他们有过节
They have history.
什么样的过节
What kind of history?
他杀了贝克特的母亲
He had Beckett's mother killed.
这是她成为警察的原因
It's why she became a cop.
她为了逮捕他付出了一切
She dedicated her life to hunting him.
那么他们为什么又见面
Okay, so, what's with the reunion?
而且为什么偏偏选今天
And why today of all days?
因为这都是布莱肯搞的鬼
Because Bracken's behind this.
我知道他曾经权倾一时
I know he was a powerful man,
但一旦被判终身监禁
but that sort of influence dries up
他的影响力很快就枯竭了
when you're serving life in prison.
你不知道和布莱肯打交道的都是些什么人
You don't know the kind of people Bracken was aligned with --
雇佣兵  毒贩子  人渣里的人渣
mercenaries, dealers, the worst of the worst.
他曾让很多人发大财
He made a lot of people rich.
其中大部分也许还欠他人情
A lot of whom may still owe him favors.
你是说是威廉·布莱肯派人袭击了你的妻子
You're saying that William Bracken ordered a hit on your wife?
贝克特毁掉了他所谓的伟业  他的人生
Beckett ruined his so-called legacy, his life.
他要让她付出代价
He's out for payback.
你真的认为布莱肯是主谋
You really think Bracken's behind this?
这样讲得通  布莱肯为人狂妄
The story tracks. Bracken is a megalomaniac
很可能怨恨贝克特毁掉他的人生
who could blame Beckett for ruining his life
虽然就凭他杀了她母亲  完全是罪有应得
even though it was justice for what he did to her mother.
等我出来你还会在这里吗
You gonna be here when I come out?
-不  -因为我给莱恩和埃斯波西托发短信
- No. - Because I texted Ryan and Esposito?
我说了不带警察
I said no cops.
你宁愿那个放满枪支的储藏柜不被发现
You'd rather there be a storage locker full of guns out there?
这不是我的问题
It's not my problem.
听着里克  如果你想成为真正的私家侦探
Look, Rick, if you want to be a real P.I.
而不是只装装样子
and not just play dress-up,
你必须改变一下你的做事方法
you're gonna have to make some changes in how you operate.
比如对我的朋友们说谎
Changes like lying to my friends?
没错  有时候就是如此
Yeah, sometimes.
有时候你甚至需要坑他们
And sometimes you're even gonna have to screw them over.
不用了  谢谢
Yeah. No, thanks.
这行里老好人可只不是垫底而已  卡塞尔
Look, nice guys don't just finish last in this business, Castle.
他们丧命的
They end up dead.
回头见
I'll see you around.
你真的很爱她  是吗
You really love her, don't you?
无法自拔
Like a house on fire.
一定感觉不错
Must be nice.
快速拨号5
Speed dial 5.
-说  -是我
- Go. - It's me.
你需要什么
What do you need?
告诉实验室我要过去  有东西需要他们化验
Tell the lab I'm coming in with something for them to test.
我要立刻知道结果
Gonna need it I.D.'d right away.
不  不
No. No, no, no, no.
别想了  我和你无话可说
Forget it. I got nothing to say to you.
真不幸
Oh, tough.
我知道贝克特来过这  而且我知道原因
I know Beckett was here, and I know why.
所以你最好让你的走狗立刻停手
So you're gonna call off your dogs right now.
否则呢  你就要写点什么来损我吗
Or what? Are you gonna write something mean about me?
否则我就以你的名义来创建一个奖学金
Or I'm gonna start a scholarship in your name
奖励给第一个在监狱洗衣房
and offer it to the children of the first inmate
打断你小腿的犯人的孩子
who shanks you in the prison laundry.
那你是白花钱
You'll be wasting your money.
原谅我不打算听你的
Oh, forgive me if I don't take your word for it.
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
你
You.
你为了你的妻子着急上火地来到这
You come in here all on fire about your wife.
可你甚至不知道她到底是谁
You don't even know who she is.
凯特·贝克特执着于解决
16 years, Kate Beckett's been obsessed
她母亲的谋杀案整整16年
with solving her mother's murder.
你真的觉得她可以就此放下这种执念
You really think she can turn off that kind of obsession?
你是说这都是她的错
Are you saying this is her fault?
我是说  只做卡塞尔夫人肯定满足不了她
I'm saying she's never gonna be happy just being Mrs. Castle.
她需要一个战场
She needs to tilt at windmills.
这念头深入骨髓  就像飞蛾都要扑火
It's in her DNA, like a moth to the flame.
我们都知道飞蛾的结局是什么
And we all know what happens to the moth in the end.
我要出去
Let me out of here.
库房是有人用偷来的身份证租的
Hey. Storage unit was rented with a stolen I.D.
我们知道谁在追踪这个
Who do we know has been chasing those?
海莉·希普顿
Hayley Shipton.
她应该有那批被盗身份的清单
She must have a list of all stolen I.D.s in that bundle.
用它追踪那些杀手到这里
Used it to track our shooters here.
还说服卡塞尔瞒着我们跟他跑了
And to convince castle to run with her instead of us.
-他在想什么  -他没想
- What the hell's he thinking? - He's not.
他只是在行动
He's reacting,
用尽一切方法来寻找贝克特
trying whatever he can to find Beckett.
这会害死他的
It's gonna get him killed.
看看这些  都是最新式的武器
Look at all this stuff. It's all next-gen weaponry.
活塞驱动  还装了热成像视镜
Piston-driven, tricked out with thermal scopes,
还有消音器
sound suppressors.
可能是职业突击队的设备
Probably some kind of professional hit squad or something.
但是谁买的呢
Yeah, but who's paying them?
以及这些怎么会和贝克特有关
And how do they connect to Beckett?
干洗店店员描述的人的画像出来了
I.D. Sketch from the dry-cleaner's came back.
这是和贝克特一起的人
The guy running with Beckett.
我们先去系统里加急搜索这个人
Let's priority-one this through the system
希望这个人的身份能让我们有些头绪
and hope that an I.D. On this guy gets us some clarity.
继续走  往蓝色货车那边去
Keep walking. Head for the blue van.
我正等着你呢
Oh, just the person I was looking for.
大多数人被枪抵着的时候
You know, most people react differently
可不是这种反应
to a gun in their side.
没错  可能是因为这种事我经历得比较多
Yeah, well, this sort of thing happens to me a lot.
我刚才还去拜访了你老板
So, I was just in there visiting with your boss.
我不知道他付你多少钱
I don't know how much he's paying you,
但肯定不值得你为此丢命
but it can't be worth your life.
你是真的什么都不知道  是吧
You really have no idea what's going on, do you?
告诉我呀
So enlighten me.
这不是我的职责
Not my job.
开门
Open it.
好好睡一觉吧
Sleep well.
我爸失踪了  我们得找到他
Dad's missing! We have to find him!
慢点说
Slow down.
你在  你在说什么
What are you -- what are you talking about?
我一直在偷偷追踪他的手机信号
I've been tracking his cellphone on the sly.
这样万一他再突然消失  我会知道的
That way, if he ever disappeared again, I'd know.
一小时前  他忽然关机了
And an hour ago, his phone suddenly went dead.
也许是没电了呢
Okay, maybe the battery just died.
不会  他不会不充电就去那
No. Not with where he went.
他去哪儿了
And where's that?
冬煞监狱  我之前追踪贝克特到那
Winterkill correctional. I tracked Beckett there earlier.
冬煞  布莱肯在那个监狱
Winterkill. That's where bracken is.
这件事似乎与他有关  所以我爸去找他了
He's connected to this somehow. That's why dad went to see him.
还不告诉我们  海莉肯定也去了
Without telling us. But I bet Hayley went along, huh?
是的  但是我给她打电话的时候
Yeah, but when I called her,
她说她在监狱跟他分开了
she said she left him at the prison.
之后就没有联系过
Hasn't heard from him since.
好吧  我去联系监狱
All right, I'll reach out to the prison,
找找他们的外围监控录像
get their external surveillance feed.
-好吧  -你要去哪
- All right. - Where are you going?
去找海莉
To get Hayley.
你别装了  我给你那针药效已经过了
You can quit faking. The dose I gave you wore off by now.
我总得试试看吧
Well, you can't blame a guy for trying.
比起《斯道姆来临》里德里克·斯道姆的把戏
You might want to try something a little more original
你更应该换换新花样了
than the trick derrick storm pulled in "Storm Fall."
你读过我的书
You read my books?
我们这行空闲时间多
Lot of downtime in my line of work.
你早期的书更好
Your earlier stuff was better.
遇到那女人之后就越写越差了
You got soft once you met the skirt.
人人都是评论家
Everyone's a critic.
坐吧
Sit.
我看你肯定不是新手了
Can't help but think you've done this before.
我是理查德·卡塞尔
Hey. Richard castle.
我想跟你握手来着  但是
I'd shake hands, but...
-你觉得挺有趣的是不是  -不不不
- You think this is funny? - No. No, no.
我只是觉得你太严肃了
I just felt like you'd be serious enough
想活跃下气氛
for the both of us.
那你看我这样严不严肃
Well, how's this for serious?
要不你告诉我你老婆在哪
You either tell me where your wife is...
要不我杀了你
or I'm gonna kill you.
这问题很简单
This is a simple question.
凯特·贝克特在哪
Where's Kate Beckett?
我不知道
I don't know.
而且就算我知道  我也不会告诉你的
And even if I did know, I wouldn't tell you.
真是奇了怪了  他们都这么说
You know, it's amazing. They all say that.
但是到最后他们都招了
And yet they all end up talking in the end.
既然我们都在问问题
You know, since we're asking questions,
或许你们能帮我补全一些信息
maybe you guys could fill in a few blanks for me.
比如  既然你们的老板不是布莱肯  谁是
For example, if bracken isn't your boss, then who is?
我觉得他还是没把这回事当真
You know what, I don't think he's taking this seriously.
也许吃点苦头可以帮他集中注意力
Maybe a little pain will help him focus.
不用了  但你知道吗
Pass. But you know what?
我现在非常想喝一杯卡布奇诺
I would kill for a nice cappuccino right now,
要多加奶泡
Extra froth.
你指望我们相信你老婆
You expect us to believe that your wife
把你蒙在鼓里
Is keeping you in the dark?
这么问不管用  你想要我们怎么审问他
Look, this isn't working. How do you want to do this?
是挨个切掉他的手指直到他说实话
Start by cutting off his fingers until he talks
还是让他直接变成婚礼上的佳肴呢
or jump straight for the wedding vegetables?
其实  我在想一种
You know, actually, I was thinking something
也许更加折磨人心的方法
maybe a little more, uh, psychological.
说实话  那东西看起来并不怎么可怕
I'm gonna be honest with you. That doesn't look that scary.
为什么不再看一下呢
Well, why don't you look again?
好吧  我要吐了
Okay, I might puke.
她在哪  卡塞尔
Where is she, Castle?
我不知道
I don't know.
她在哪
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know!
她在哪
Where is she?
我什么也不知道
I don't know anything.
最后一次看见卡塞尔是在监狱外面
The last time I saw Castle was outside the prison.
我还以为当过警察就能明白
You'd think an ex-cop would understand
妨碍司法公正是怎么回事
obstruction of justice.
是啊  尤其是她如果为此被捕的话
Yeah, especially since arresting her for it
她的侦探执照也会被吊销
will torpedo her investigator's license.
你们别想吓唬我  两位
You're not scaring me, guys.
你以为我们在闹着玩吗
You think we're playing?
卡塞尔是我们的兄弟  所以你最好
Castle's one of us, which means you better
乖乖坦白  否则全城的警察
come clean right now, or every cop in this city
都会想办法找你的麻烦
is gonna make it their mission to jam you up.
我能理解你们的愤怒
I understand the passion.
但我必须维护我的职业信誉
But I have a reputation to uphold.
如果我的客户认为
My clients think that I roll over
警察一吓唬我  我就投降
every time a cop says "Boo,"
那我就别在这行混了
I'm looking for a new line of work.
该死  我爸爸现在生死未卜
Damn it, my dad's in trouble!
如果你知道他在哪里  你必须告诉我们
If you know anything about where he is, you have to tell us.
阿丽克西斯  没那么简单的
Alexis, it's not that simple.
不  就是这么简单
Yes, it is.
求你了
Please.
好吧  我的确隐瞒了一些事
Okay, there is something I kept to myself,
不过对你们没什么帮助的
but it's not gonna help you.
那是条死路
It's a dead end.
快说
Spill.
我在储存室那碰到个女人
There was a woman at the storage locker.
我们过了几招
We mixed it up a little.
她踢我时  靴子上的东西蹭到了我衣服上
When she kicked me, something transferred from her boot.
我找地方化验了  是木馏油
I had a lab test it. It's creosote.
它是煤焦油的一种
It's a form of coal tar
主要用于处理铁路上的枕木
primarily used to treat railway ties.
有成千上万这种枕木被用在地铁轨道上
There are tens of thousands of those ties used in the subway.
你有实验室报告的复本吗
You get a copy of the lab report?
有
Yeah.
不  枕木不是地铁里的
No, tie's not from the subway.
什么  你怎么知道
What? How do you know?
没有任何钢铁粉尘或其它污染物的迹象
No traces of any steel dust or any other pollutants.
我推测那铁路上的枕木是新的
My guess is that the railroad tie's new.
我打电话给运输署  问这些东西储存在哪
I'll call MTA. See where they store those things.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她在哪
Where is she?
你妻子在哪  卡塞尔
Where's your wife, Castle?
我不知道  我发誓
I don't know! I swear!
你答错了
That is the wrong answer.
告诉我你妻子在哪
Tell me where your wife is.
告诉我她在哪
Tell me where she is.
她在哪
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know!
卡塞尔  任何女人都不值得你牺牲自己
Come on, Castle. No woman is worth dying for.
快说  她在哪
Come on. Where is she?!
我相信你说得是实话  真的
I believe that you're telling the truth. I do.
我相信你对我们说得都是实话
I believe that you're telling me the truth.
但很不幸  那意味着你没有活着的价值了
But unfortunately, that means it's time for you to die.
真抱歉
Sorry about that.
受死吧
Lights out.
卡塞尔  你没事吧
Castle. Are you okay?
你去哪了  为什么连电话也不打
Where have you been? Why haven't you called?
我没法打
I couldn't.
凯特  出什么事了
Kate, what's going on?
我...
I...
我得走了
I've got to go.
不  别走  凯特  你为什么瞒着我
No, no! No, Kate -- Kate, why are you shutting me out?
卡塞尔  我爱你
Castle, I love you.
凯特  凯特
Kate. Kate.
凯特
Kate.
卡塞尔  老兄  你没事吧
Castle! Hey, man, you okay?
贝克特  她刚才在这  她刚才在这里
Beckett -- she was here. She was here!
什么  在哪
What? Where?
爸爸
Dad!
我没事  我没事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
没事了
It's okay.
没找到凯萨琳·贝克特  长官
No sign of Katherine Beckett, sir.
特警队说整个大楼都搜遍了
E.S.U. says the building is secure.
没发现贝克特的踪影
There's no sign of Beckett.
贝克特为什么不信任我
Why doesn't Beckett trust me?
她信任你
She does.
那她为什么把我蒙在鼓里
Then why is she keeping me in the dark?
-我不需要人保护  -不  你需要
- I don't need protecting. - Yes, you do.
你是个作家  爸爸
You're a writer, dad.
你俩在一起时很厉害
And you and Beckett are magic together.
但你并没受过她那样的训练  没有她的本事
But you don't have her training or her skill set.
去年你失踪的时候
When you disappeared last year...
那两个月我都以为你死了
I thought you were dead for two months.
今天你失踪的时候我真的很害怕
And then you went missing today, and I was so scared.
亲爱的
Honey --
贝克特保守秘密是有原因的
Beckett has a reason for keeping quiet.
如果你爱她  你就要相信她
If you love her, you have to trust her.
我们还在等什么  给她点苦头
Finally. What are we waiting for? Let's go give her hell.
-卡塞尔别着急  -我们已经找出
- Castle, wait. - We got a positive I.D.
和贝克特在一起的那人的身份
on the guy running with Beckett.
很好  是谁
Great. Who is he?
他叫维克拉姆·辛格
His name is Vikram Singh.
他是个初级分析员
He's a low-level analyst
供职于总检察长调查办公室
for the attorney general's investigative office.
在华盛顿吗
In D.C.?
贝克特在那儿工作过
That's where Beckett worked.
对  但那是两年前了
Yeah, but that was two years ago,
她从没提过一个叫维克拉姆的人
and she never mentioned anyone named Vikram.
据我们所知  他们俩没有交集
Yeah, as far as we can tell, their paths never crossed.
他几个月前才开始在那工作
He's only been on the job a few months.
那贝克特怎么会认识他
Then how would Beckett know him?
我们得联系蕾切尔·麦考德
We need to call Rachel McCord.
她是贝克特的搭档
She was Beckett's partner.
麦考德已经死了  卡塞尔
McCord's dead, Castle.
于昨天的一次车祸中遇害
Killed yesterday in an automobile accident,
遇害的还有她那组的其他三名成员
Along with three other members of her team.
这肯定不是巧合
That can't be a coincidence.
肯定不是
It's not.
她组内的最后一名成员也于昨晚
The last member of her team was stabbed to death
在一家俱乐部中被刺死
at a club that same night.
有人看到他和一位性感褐色头发女子调情
Witnesses saw him flirting with a hot brunette.
这都说不通
This doesn't make any sense.
这和布莱肯有什么关系
What does any of this have to do with Bracken?
我们去问她吧
Well, let's go ask her.
你嘴上说你有很多空闲时间
For someone who says they've got a lot of downtime,
但你其实忙得很啊
you sure have been a busy girl.
谋划车祸  在华盛顿行刺
Staging car accidents, stabbings in D.C.,
在纽约持枪绑架我
kidnapping me at gunpoint in New York.
告诉我  杀手会攒很多常客飞行里程吗
Tell me, do assassins get frequent-flier miles?
对了  你不会坐商务机对吧
Ah, but you didn't fly commercial, did you?
我们在每趟华盛顿飞来的航班上核对你的照片
We ran your photo against every flight from D.C.
所以你要么是开车要么乘私人飞机
So you either road-tripped it or you took a private jet.
考虑到你的那个军械库
And given your arsenal,
你们肯定坐得起私人飞机
you people clearly have the resources.
我不太确定你们想从我这知道些什么
I'm not really sure what you're expecting here.
泪流满面地坦白吗  想都别想
A tearful confession? Not gonna happen.
我们希望你够聪明  能想明白
Well, we are expecting that you're smart enough to know
现在是想办法减轻罪责的时候
that it's C.Y.A. Time.
听着  除非你有一口袋的蜘蛛
Look, unless you've got a bag of spiders,
我没什么好说的
we're done here.
你跟我说我什么都不知道
You know, you told me I had no idea what was going on,
你说得对
And you were right.
但现在我有点头绪了
But now I've got the edge of it,
不管有没有你的帮助
and I'm gonna keep on peeling it back
我都会彻查到底
until I know everything, with or without your help.
我还是建议你配合一点  能少坐点牢
I'll recommend the "With." It comes with less prison time.
跟我开口的下场相比  坐牢简直不算什么
Prison's a picnic compared to what happens to me if I talk.
你得接受这个事实
You need to make your peace with the fact that
你妻子将不久于人世了
your wife isn't long for this world.
别说这么肯定  你们团队开始有五个人
Don't be so sure. Your team started out with five.
有三个已经死了  而你坐在这
Three of you are dead, and you're sitting right here.
那还剩下一个人  你的老大
That leaves one -- your boss.
贝克特对付这一个人  我比较乐观
And Beckett against one guy? I like those odds.
你凭什么觉得就只有一队人马呢
What makes you think there's only one team in play?
很好
All right.
我刚和华盛顿总检察长助理通过话
I just got off the phone with an assistant A.G. in D.C.,
一个叫艾莉森·海德的人
An Allison Hyde.
她负责调查她的同事遇害的案子
She's leading the investigation in the deaths of her people.
她明天早上第一班飞机过来
She's up on the first plane in the morning
把那个袭击者移交联邦警察监禁
to take our hitter into federal custody.
她知不知道这个叫维克拉姆的人
Does she have any idea of this Vikram guy's connection
跟贝克特之间的关联
to Beckett?
没有  但她正在调阅他的档案
No, but she's pulling his records.
所以  现在我们没线索了
So, we're nowhere.
有枪  有枪  枪
Gun! Gun! Gun!
所有人  趴下
Everybody, get down!
小心
Look out!
-我得做点什么  -别犯傻
- I'm gonna do something. - Don't be stupid.
不然还有什么乐趣呢
Where's the fun in that?
枪手被击倒
Shooter's down!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
过来
Come on.
警官  躺下
L.T. Stay down.
有两位警员中枪
We got two officers down.
赶快
Hurry up!
亲爱的  别看
Oh, sweetie, don't look.
她为什么这么做
Why did she do it?
她知道自己没法逃脱
There's no way she thought she could escape.
她不是要逃脱
It wasn't about escape.
她被捕时就已经知道了自己的下场
She knew her fate was sealed as soon as she got caught.
所以她才用自己的方式自我了断
That's why she went out on her own terms.
同时让我们毫无头绪
And made sure we stay in the dark.
该死  凯特  你在哪
Damn it, Kate. Where are you?